MOK CHI HONG

+6016-420 7760 · mokchi2324@hotmail.com · https://joseph-portfolio-ugu2y6sala-as.a.run.app/ Butterworth, Penang, Malaysia

FULL STACK WEB & MOBILE DEVELOPER

Full stack developer with 3 years of working experience in both mobile and web development. My proficient is in developing full stack web application using Laravel / Yii2 Framework, mobile application with Flutter and backend RESTful APIs. I specialized in creating user-friendly applications by writing clean, reusable and maintainable code. I'm passionate about staying updated with latest trend in web and mobile development. Currently seeking job opportunity in related field. I have experience leading a team and also capable of working with minimal supervision. I love to accept new challenges and I'm a fast learner.

SKILL

Flutter	PHP	RESTful API	Git
Laravel	TypeScript	MySQL	Docker
Yii2	ReactJS	Tailwind CSS	YOLOv5

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Silkron Technology Sdn Bhd Lead Software Engineer

Jan 2023 - Present

Responsibilities

- Lead and manage team by providing mentorship and guidance.
- Design and develop custom application to meet customer's requirements.
- Design and develop mobile application using Flutter framework.
- Deploy and maintain mobile application on Google play and Apple app store.
- Develop and integrate RESTful APIs into mobile application.
- Continuously optimize app and API performance to enhance user satisfaction and overall efficiency
- · Assign task and evaluate man-days for team.
- · Code base version control with git and SVN.

Accomplishments:

- Revamp entire mobile app and cloud APIs legacy code base by writing clean and maintainable code to reduce bugs and errors.
- Develop and deploy various customize mobile app.

Silkron Technology Sdn Bhd Software Engineer

June 2021 - Jan 2023

Responsibilities

- Design, implement and deploy web application using Yii2 Framework and JS
- · Develop and maintain WeChat Mini Program
- Al Model training with YOLOv5 object detection algorithm and image labeling using PaddleSeg.
- Develop RESTful APIs for mini program and mobile application.
- Design, develop and maintain mobile application using Flutter framework.
- · Code base version control.

Accomplishments:

- Train AI model for smart fridge project which has above 96% accuracy.
- Develop and deploy WeChat mini program for China client using WeChat H5 framework.

Silkron Technology Sdn Bhd Internship

Jan 2021 - June 2021

Responsibilities

- · Design, develop and maintain web-based solution with MySQL, JS and Yii2 PHP Framework
- Assist senior debug and solve web related problems.

Zepheus Corporate Services Sdn Bhd Internship

June 2020 - Sept 2020

Responsibilities

• Design and develop responsive web-base secretary system using MySQL, JS, Jquery and Laravel PHP Framework.

EDUCATION

University of Greenwich

Bachelor Of Science (HONS) Computing

3.91 CGPA | 2019 - 2021

- · First class honours
- · Best student award
- Develop a fully functioning web-based comic website with Laravel and deploy it on Microsoft Azure.

SEGi College Penang

Diploma In Information Technology

3.62 CGPA | 2016 - 2018

- Vice president of Multi-Tech Society
- Champion of SEGi Video Competition

LANGUAGE

Chinese English Malay

ADDITIONAL SKILL

GCP WeChat H5 Adobe packages Excel VBA
C# C++ Java Python